Connections is a personals list for people on Are.na.
Meet through what you collect and create—
for friendship, collaboration, romance, or just someone new to talk to.
If you know Are.na, you know.
It’s where I go for visual research, good books, hot sites.
Sometimes solo, sometimes with friends.
But the people make it what it is.
There’s been a longstanding joke that Are.na should have a dating app.
Connections is for finding friendship, collaboration,
and all that based on Are.na collections.
No algorithm, and no upgrades
because it only took six hours to make and runs on Are.na itself.
You connect your account and answer some prompts with blocks and channels.
Sort of a window into your mind.
Send someone a message, and it opens a private Are.na channel
for just the two of you.
Meet someone, see what develops.
I hope you have fun with it.